The Darkest Hour Of Humanity
Invasion Roswell is a science fiction, action film directed by David Flores.
After the American Army shot down a UFO in 1947, generations of elite commandos
were secretly trained to deal with the aliens' feared return.
However, the extra-terrestrials never came back
and the elite force was disbanded.
Sixty-six years after the Roswell crash, the aliens are invading Earth and
only the over-the-hill retired commandos can stop them.
Linda, played by Denise Crosby.
Patrick, played by Greg Evigan.
David, played by Daniel Hugh Kelly.
Burkis, played by Stephen Billington.
James, played by Clarence Smith.
Tech, played by Iliana Lazarova.
Debris found by a rancher in 1947 near Roswell, New Mexico, has become the basis for UFO conspiracy theories
alleging that the United States military recovered a crashed extraterrestrial spacecraft.
After metallic and rubber debris was recovered by Roswell Army Air Field personnel, the
United States Army Air Forces announced possession of a "flying disc".
This announcement made international headlines, but was retracted within a day.
The debris was from a complex and uncrewed military balloon train consisting of linked balloons and assorted equipment, operated from the
nearby Alamogordo Army Air Field as part of the top-secret Project Mogul, a program intended to detect Soviet nuclear tests.
To obscure the purpose and source of the debris, the army reported
that it was merely a conventional weather balloon.
In 1978, retired United States Air Force officer Jesse Marcel revealed that the army's weather balloon
claim had been a cover story, and speculated that the debris was of extraterrestrial origin.
Popularized by the 1980 book The Roswell Incident, this speculation became the basis for long-lasting and increasingly complex and contradictory conspiracy theories, which over time expanded the incident to include governments
concealing evidence of extraterrestrial beings, grey aliens, multiple crashed flying saucers, alien corpses and autopsies, and the reverse engineering of extraterrestrial technology, none of which have any factual basis.
In the 1990s, the Air Force published multiple reports which established that the
incident was related to Project Mogul, and not debris from a UFO.
Despite this and a general lack of evidence, many UFO proponents claim that the Roswell debris was
in fact derived from an alien craft, and accuse the US government of a cover-up.
The conspiracy narrative has become a trope in science
fiction literature, film, and television.
The town of Roswell promotes itself as a destination for UFO-associated tourism.
The tone is thought_provoking.